404.216.1379 kia@lakiaross.com lakiaross.github.io

Graphic design professional with experience in web design, front-end development, book design, presentation materials, and corporate publications. A unique self-starter/team-player hybrid able to deliver successful projects from concept to completion to client on time.

Professional History

Freelance and Contract Graphic Designer | 2007 - Present

- Developed logo for specialized Machine-to-Machine Trusted Behaviors project at Georgia Tech Research Institute. (*Winter 2014 2015*)
- Designed vector graphics, signs, and banners for Advanced Color Imaging. (Spring 2014 Winter 2014)
- Developed device-responsive Historic Norcross Holiday Tour of Homes and Pro Sound Rentals Atlanta websites with Wordpress and Bootstrap. (*Fall 2014*)
- Developed video portfolio website for Vanderkloot Film & Television using Wordpress, jQuery, and Bootstrap. (*Spring/Summer 2014*)
- Developed Wordpress-based e-commerce website for Little Mammoth Media. (Fall 2013-Spring 2014)
- Custom Wordpress template modification and additional front-end development for TotallyCustomWallpapers.com. (Winter 2013-Spring 2014)
- Coordinated with 3dMD, a global leader in medical imaging, in-house marketing team to re-brand the company with new identity, website, publications, and trade banners. (*Spring 2012 Fall 2014*)

Graphic Design Instructor | Savannah College of Art and Design, August - October 2010

- Developed and implemented a series of introductory workshops for students enrolled in the Community Education program who were interested in pursuing a career in graphic design.
- Taught the basic principles of design and software commonly used to produce design projects.

Senior Graphic Designer | Woodruff Arts Center, January 2002 - April 2007

- Provided graphic solutions for a broad spectrum of Woodruff Arts Center Administration projects (principally projects for the CEO, VPs, and Directors).
- Developed and maintained branding initiatives and lent graphic support to creative counterparts throughout Woodruff's member divisions (High Museum of Art, Atlanta Symphony Orchestra, Alliance Theatre, and Atlanta College of Art).
- Required to be self-sufficient, pro-active, and able to work effectively as a key member of the creative team as well as a frequent consultant and contributor to the design efforts of Woodruff's Public Relations and Initiatives Department on a vast array of projects.

Pertinent Skills

Technical Expertise:

- Front-end: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Sass
- CMS: Wordpress
- Back-end: PHP, MySQL
- Currently learning: Python, Less, AJAX, AngularJS and NodeJS

Software (Mac):

Adobe Creative Suite CC: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, Dreamweaver, Flash Microsoft Office: Word, PowerPoint, Excel

Education